

INFO Address

14B Agios Stefanos, Attica, Greece 14565

Contact

info@panteliskassotis.com

linkedin.com/in/pkassotis

EDUCATION

University of the Aegean

2013-2014

Business Administration, Management and Operations. Eventually dropped out to pursue software development.

CERTIFICATIONS

Harvard University

2020

Multiple Certificates:
Professional proficiency in
computer science for web
programming, mobile
apps, game development
and artificial intelligence.

Certificates available upon request

PANTELIS KASSOTIS

Software Engineer / Game Developer

ABOUT ME

Got full stack experience creating and managing websites, mobile apps and GUIs from the concept stage all the way to publishing. I Love learning new things and tools every day. Favorite hobbies include animation, music, and kayaking.

EXPERIENCE

Studio Head / Lead Programmer

TETHORAX SOFTWORKS (2020 - Present)

- I'm in charge of the development and publishing process of all our mobile games, from the concept stage all the way to the app store.
- The game engine we use to develop our games is GDevelop, an open source project of which I'm an active member
- I created the first iteration of the engine's mobile app, and contributed 6265 words to its Greek translation using the Crowdin localization platform.

Tech Columnist / Gaming Expert

HackerNoon (2021 - Present)

- Publishing game development stories and expertise for 3,000,000+ curious and insightful monthly readers.
- Helping brands and independent game development studios advertise their gaming related products.